// Short circuit


let exp = "faraz" || (true + false) + 5 && " " || "true";
console.log(exp)

let b = 3;
let exp1 = (1 + 2) + ++b || 5 && 0 ; 
console.log(exp1)

let a=5;
let exp2 = 32 && true - ++a && " " || "true" ;
console.log(exp2);

let exp3 = (true + 3) * 5 && undefined || "faraz" + 5;
console.log(exp3);

let exp4 = 32 + "abc" || (true + false) + false || + 5 || "true";
console.log(exp4)

let exp5 = false || (true + true) + 15 && "" || 50;
console.log(exp5)

let exp6 = (true + false) + 5 || false + 8 + "abc" || "true";
console.log(exp6)

let exp7 = "faraz" || false + 10 || "true";
console.log(exp7)

let exp8 = 12 + (false + false) + true && null || "faraz";
console.log(exp8)

let exp9 = (false + true + false + 2) || "faraz" && false || 1 + 10;
console.log(exp9)

let exp10 = (true + false) + 5 || false + 8 + "abc" || "true";
console.log(exp10)

let exp11 = (true + false) * 3 && "" || false + true - (12 + true + true + false);
console.log(exp11)


// Q2: Create a mobile brand and model filtering app with filter mobile brand and then second
// dropdown have same brand model in second dropdown and a single search button when click
// the selected brand and model have shown in html body

var mobiles = {
    iphone: {
      iphone7: {
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 2",
        memory: {
          ram: 12,
          storage: 512,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: 200,
            ultrawide: 12,
            telephoto: 10,
            telephotoPeriscope: 10,
          },
          front: 10,
        },
        battery: 5000,
        operatingSystem: "Android 13",
        specialFeatures: ["S Pen support", "Ultrasonic fingerprint sensor"],
      },
      iphone8: {
        processor: "Snapdragon 12 Gen 5",
        memory: {
          ram: 8,
          storage: 256,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: 180,
            ultrawide: 15,
            telephoto: 10,
            telephotoPeriscope: 20,
          },
          front: 12,
        },
        battery: 8000,
        operatingSystem: "iphone 8",
        specialFeatures: ["S Pen support", "Ultrasonic fingerprint sensor"],
      },
      iphone8plus: {
        processor: "Snapdragon 5 Gen 6",
        memory: {
          ram: 8,
          storage: 128,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: 160,
            ultrawide: 18,
            telephoto: 10,
            telephotoPeriscope: 8,
          },
          front: 16,
        },
        battery: 5000,
        operatingSystem: "iphone 8",
        specialFeatures: ["S Pen support", "Ultrasonic fingerprint sensor"],
      },
      iphoneX: {
        processor: "Snapdragon 5 Gen 4",
        memory: {
          ram: 8,
          storage: 256,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: 130,
            ultrawide: 16,
            telephoto: 10,
            telephotoPeriscope: 18,
          },
          front: 14,
        },
        battery: 6000,
        operatingSystem: "iphone X",
        specialFeatures: ["S Pen support", "Ultrasonic fingerprint sensor"],
      },
      iphone11: {
        processor: "Snapdragon 7 Gen 9",
        memory: {
          ram: 16,
          storage: 512,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: 150,
            ultrawide: 24,
            telephoto: 16,
            telephotoPeriscope: 10,
          },
          front: 20,
        },
        battery: 10000,
        operatingSystem: "iphone 11",
        specialFeatures: ["S Pen support", "Ultrasonic fingerprint sensor"],
      },
    },
    xiomi: {
      redmiA2: {
        modelName: "Mi 12 Pro",
        display: {
          size: 6.73,
          resolution: "3200 x 1440",
          panelType: "AMOLED",
          refreshRate: 120,
        },
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 1",
        memory: {
          ram: 8,
          storage: 256,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: "50MP",
            ultrawide: "50MP",
            telephoto: "48MP",
          },
          front: "32MP",
        },
        battery: 4600,
        operatingSystem: "Android 12",
        specialFeatures: ["Wireless charging", "In-display fingerprint sensor"],
      },
      redmi10: {
        modelName: "Mi 8 Pro",
        display: {
          size: 5.73,
          resolution: "3000 x 1320",
          panelType: "AMOLED",
          refreshRate: 100,
        },
        processor: "Snapdragon 7 Gen 5",
        memory: {
          ram: 12,
          storage: 256,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: "50MP",
            ultrawide: "50MP",
            telephoto: "48MP",
          },
          front: "32MP",
        },
        battery: 5000,
        operatingSystem: "Android 11",
        specialFeatures: ["Wireless charging", "In-display fingerprint sensor"],
      },
  
      redmi11: {
        modelName: "Mi 14 Pro",
        display: {
          size: 6.0,
          resolution: "3000 x 1240",
          panelType: "AMOLED",
          refreshRate: 150,
        },
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 4",
        memory: {
          ram: 12,
          storage: 512,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: "50MP",
            ultrawide: "50MP",
            telephoto: "48MP",
          },
          front: "32MP",
        },
        battery: 8000,
        operatingSystem: "Android 12",
        specialFeatures: ["Wireless charging", "In-display fingerprint sensor"],
      },
  
      redmi12: {
        modelName: "Mi 12 Pro",
        display: {
          size: 7.4,
          resolution: "3200 x 1440",
          panelType: "AMOLED",
          refreshRate: 180,
        },
        processor: "Snapdragon 12 Gen 1",
        memory: {
          ram: 12,
          storage: 512,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: "50MP",
            ultrawide: "50MP",
            telephoto: "48MP",
          },
          front: "32MP",
        },
        battery: 8000,
        operatingSystem: "Android 13",
        specialFeatures: ["Wireless charging", "In-display fingerprint sensor"],
      },
  
      redmi13: {
        modelName: "Mi 14 Pro",
        display: {
          size: 8.03,
          resolution: "4200 x 1540",
          panelType: "AMOLED",
          refreshRate: 100,
        },
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 6",
        memory: {
          ram: 12,
          storage: 256,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: "50MP",
            ultrawide: "50MP",
            telephoto: "48MP",
          },
          front: "32MP",
        },
        battery: 10000,
        operatingSystem: "Android 13",
        specialFeatures: ["Wireless charging", "In-display fingerprint sensor"],
      },
  
      redmi13C: {
        modelName: "Mi 14 Pro",
        display: {
          size: 8.43,
          resolution: "4200 x 1340",
          panelType: "AMOLED",
          refreshRate: 100,
        },
        processor: "Snapdragon 9 Gen 5",
        memory: {
          ram: 12,
          storage: 512,
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            main: "50MP",
            ultrawide: "50MP",
            telephoto: "48MP",
          },
          front: "32MP",
        },
        battery: 10000,
        operatingSystem: "Android 13",
        specialFeatures: ["Wireless charging", "In-display fingerprint sensor"],
      },
    },
    realme: {
      realmiNote50: {
        brand: "Realme",
        model: " hypothetical model ", // Replace with specific model name
        display: {
          size: "6.5 inches",
          resolution: "FHD+ (1080 x 2400 pixels)",
          type: "AMOLED",
        },
        processor: "Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 1", // Replace with specific processor
        memory: {
          ram: "8GB",
          storage: "128GB",
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            resolution: "64MP (wide) + 8MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (macro)",
          },
          front: {
            resolution: "16MP",
          },
        },
        battery: {
          capacity: "5000mAh",
          fastCharging: "65W",
        },
        operatingSystem: "Android 12",
        specialFeatures: [
          "In-display fingerprint sensor",
          "3.5mm headphone jack",
        ],
      },
      realmiC67: {
        brand: "Realme",
        model: " hypothetical model ", // Replace with specific model name
        display: {
          size: "6.7 inches",
          resolution: "FHD+ (1280 x 2100 pixels)",
          type: "AMOLED",
        },
        processor: "Qualcomm Snapdragon 6 Gen 4", // Replace with specific processor
        memory: {
          ram: "8GB",
          storage: "256GB",
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            resolution: "64MP (wide) + 8MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (macro)",
          },
          front: {
            resolution: "14MP",
          },
        },
        battery: {
          capacity: "5000mAh",
          fastCharging: "65W",
        },
        operatingSystem: "Android 11",
        specialFeatures: [
          "In-display fingerprint sensor",
          "3.5mm headphone jack",
        ],
      },
      realmiC53: {
        brand: "Realme",
        model: " hypothetical model ", // Replace with specific model name
        display: {
          size: "7. 1inches",
          resolution: "FHD+ (1180 x 2500 pixels)",
          type: "AMOLED",
        },
        processor: "Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 6", // Replace with specific processor
        memory: {
          ram: "12GB",
          storage: "128GB",
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            resolution: "64MP (wide) + 8MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (macro)",
          },
          front: {
            resolution: "18MP",
          },
        },
        battery: {
          capacity: "8000mAh",
          fastCharging: "65W",
        },
        operatingSystem: "Android 12",
        specialFeatures: [
          "In-display fingerprint sensor",
          "3.5mm headphone jack",
        ],
      },
      realmi9: {
        brand: "Realme",
        model: " hypothetical model ", // Replace with specific model name
        display: {
          size: "7.2 inches",
          resolution: "FHD+ (1180 x 2200 pixels)",
          type: "AMOLED",
        },
        processor: "Qualcomm Snapdragon 9 Gen 6", // Replace with specific processor
        memory: {
          ram: "12GB",
          storage: "256GB",
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            resolution: "64MP (wide) + 8MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (macro)",
          },
          front: {
            resolution: "24MP",
          },
        },
        battery: {
          capacity: "10000mAh",
          fastCharging: "75W",
        },
        operatingSystem: "Android 12",
        specialFeatures: [
          "In-display fingerprint sensor",
          "3.5mm headphone jack",
        ],
      },
      realmi9i: {
        brand: "Realme",
        model: " hypothetical model ", // Replace with specific model name
        display: {
          size: "6.9 inches",
          resolution: "FHD+ (1480 x 2400 pixels)",
          type: "AMOLED",
        },
        processor: "Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 1", // Replace with specific processor
        memory: {
          ram: "12GB",
          storage: "512GB",
        },
        camera: {
          rear: {
            resolution: "64MP (wide) + 8MP (ultrawide) + 2MP (macro)",
          },
          front: {
            resolution: "16MP",
          },
        },
        battery: {
          capacity: "2000mAh",
          fastCharging: "70W",
        },
        operatingSystem: "Android 13",
        specialFeatures: [
          "In-display fingerprint sensor",
          "3.5mm headphone jack",
        ],
      },
    },
    samsung: {
      samsung_Galaxy_S24: {
        brand: "Samsung",
        model: "Galaxy S24 Ultra", // Replace with specific model
  
        // Display
        displaySize: 6.8, // Inches
        displayResolution: "3088x1440",
        displayType: "AMOLED",
  
        // Processor & Memory
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 2", // Replace with actual processor
        ram: 12, // GB
        storage: 512, // GB
  
        // Cameras
        rearCamera: {
          megapixel: 108,
          features: ["10x Optical Zoom", "Night Mode", "8K Video Recording"],
        },
        frontCamera: {
          megapixel: 40,
        },
  
        // Battery
        batteryCapacity: 5000, // mAh
        fastCharging: "45W Super Fast Charging",
  
        // Operating System
        os: "Android 14",
  
        // Additional Specs (Optional)
        fingerprintSensor: true,
        waterResistance: "IP68",
        expandableStorage: false,
      },
      samsung_Galaxy_S51: {
        brand: "Samsung",
        model: "Galaxy S51 Pro", // Replace with specific model
  
        // Display
        displaySize: 7.2, // Inches
        displayResolution: "3088x1440",
        displayType: "AMOLED",
  
        // Processor & Memory
        processor: "Snapdragon 9 Gen 4", // Replace with actual processor
        ram: 8, // GB
        storage: 256, // GB
  
        // Cameras
        rearCamera: {
          megapixel: 112,
          features: ["10x Optical Zoom", "Night Mode", "8K Video Recording"],
        },
        frontCamera: {
          megapixel: 40,
        },
  
        // Battery
        batteryCapacity: 8000, // mAh
        fastCharging: "45W Super Fast Charging",
  
        // Operating System
        os: "Android 11",
  
        // Additional Specs (Optional)
        fingerprintSensor: true,
        waterResistance: "IP68",
        expandableStorage: false,
      },
      samsung_Galaxy_Prime: {
        brand: "Samsung",
        model: "Galaxy Prime Ultra", // Replace with specific model
  
        // Display
        displaySize: 7.4, // Inches
        displayResolution: "3088x1440",
        displayType: "AMOLED",
  
        // Processor & Memory
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 10", // Replace with actual processor
        ram: 8, // GB
        storage: 256, // GB
  
        // Cameras
        rearCamera: {
          megapixel: 108,
          features: ["10x Optical Zoom", "Night Mode", "8K Video Recording"],
        },
        frontCamera: {
          megapixel: 40,
        },
  
        // Battery
        batteryCapacity: 5000, // mAh
        fastCharging: "45W Super Fast Charging",
  
        // Operating System
        os: "Android 13",
  
        // Additional Specs (Optional)
        fingerprintSensor: true,
        waterResistance: "IP68",
        expandableStorage: false,
      },
      samsung_Galaxy_S46: {
        brand: "Samsung",
        model: "Galaxy S46 Ultra", // Replace with specific model
  
        // Display
        displaySize: 5.11, // Inches
        displayResolution: "3088x1440",
        displayType: "AMOLED",
  
        // Processor & Memory
        processor: "Snapdragon 8 Gen 2", // Replace with actual processor
        ram: 12, // GB
        storage: 512, // GB
  
        // Cameras
        rearCamera: {
          megapixel: 108,
          features: ["10x Optical Zoom", "Night Mode", "8K Video Recording"],
        },
        frontCamera: {
          megapixel: 40,
        },
  
        // Battery
        batteryCapacity: 20000, // mAh
        fastCharging: "65W Super Fast Charging",
  
        // Operating System
        os: "Android 14",
  
        // Additional Specs (Optional)
        fingerprintSensor: true,
        waterResistance: "IP68",
        expandableStorage: false,
      },
      samsung_Galaxy_S77: {
        brand: "Samsung",
        model: "Galaxy S77 Ultra", // Replace with specific model
  
        // Display
        displaySize: 8.5, // Inches
        displayResolution: "3088x1440",
        displayType: "AMOLED",
  
        // Processor & Memory
        processor: "Snapdragon 12 Gen 24", // Replace with actual processor
        ram: 12, // GB
        storage: 512, // GB
  
        // Cameras
        rearCamera: {
          megapixel: 158,
          features: ["10x Optical Zoom", "Night Mode", "8K Video Recording"],
        },
        frontCamera: {
          megapixel: 40,
        },
  
        // Battery
        batteryCapacity: 20000, // mAh
        fastCharging: "85W Super Fast Charging",
  
        // Operating System
        os: "Android 14",
  
        // Additional Specs (Optional)
        fingerprintSensor: true,
        waterResistance: "IP68",
        expandableStorage: true,
      },
    },
  };



  let brand = document.getElementById('brand');
let model = document.getElementById('model');


var brandsKeys = Object.keys(mobiles)

for(var i = 0;i<brandsKeys.length;i++){

brand.innerHTML += `<option>${brandsKeys[i]}</option>`

}

function selectBrand(){
    let selectBrand = brand.value;
    let allModels = Object.keys(mobiles[selectBrand]);

    for(var i = 0;i<allModels.length;i++){
        model.innerHTML += `<option>${allModels[i]}</option>` 
    }

    console.log("allModels: ",allModels)
}

function showbtn(){
    let Card = document.getElementById('cardPortion');

    var filterObj = mobiles[brand.value][model.value];

    console.log(mobiles[brand.value][model.value])

    Card.innerHTML = `<div class="card" style="width: 18rem;">
  <div class="card-body">
    <h5 class="card-title" Brand: >${filterObj.brand}</h5>
    <h5 class="card-subtitle mb-2 text-body-secondary" Operating System:>${filterObj.operatingSystem}</h5>
    <h5 class="card-text">Processor: ${filterObj.processor}</h5>
  </div>
</div>`

}